Rare Pamphlet Collection 6034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Box: 23, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Economic recovery in the light of Catholic principles, 1933; Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Author: Aloysius J. Hogan
- Box: 23, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A first step toward school integration, 1958; Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Author: Anna. Holden
    Notes: In cooperation with the Nashville CORE group
- Box: 23, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Eugene V. Debs, what his neighbors say of him, 1914; Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    Author: James H. Hollingsworth
- Box: 23, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: What if they are red?, 1948; Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
    Author: John P. Holly
- Box: 23, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The individual in a dynamic world, 1945; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    Author: Eugene Holman
  - Item 2: Machinery and social progress, 1930; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Box: 23, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Trade Union Unity League today: its structure, policy, program and growth, 1934; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
    Author: Nathaniel Honig
- Box: 23, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Heresy, yes--conspiracy, no!, 1952; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
    Author: Sidney Hook
- Box: 23, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Working-class education, 1924; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Author: J. F. Horrabin; Winifred Horrabin
  - Item 2: Socialism in pictures and figures, 1934; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
    Author: J. F. Horrabin; G. D. H. Cole
- Box: 23, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Hotel wages tables computed for 30 and 31 days: daily calculations from $5.00 to $100.00 monthly, 1918; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
    Notes: Hotel proprietors employing a large number of help, use either monthly table at their discretion.
- Box: 23, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: I am a woman worker: a scrapbook of autobiographies, 1936; Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    Author: Andria Taylor Hourwich; Gladys L. Palmer
- Box: 24, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: How legislative inquisitions stifle integration and social progress, 1960; Publication (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Box: 24, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: How to raise wages without increasing prices, Publication (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Author: Walter Reuther
- Box: 24, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The ever-full treasury, 1950; Publication (Box 24, Folder 3)
    Author: Eugene Leslie Howard
- Box: 24, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The labor spy: a survey of industrial espionage, 1921; Publication (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Author: Sidney Coe Howard; Richard C. Cabot
- Box: 24, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The closed or open shop?, 1910; Publication (Box 24, Folder 5)
    Author: Elbert Hubbard
- Box: 24, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Storm over Bridges, 1941; Publication (Box 24, Folder 6)
    Author: Leo Huberman
- Box: 24, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Post-war jobs for veterans, Negroes, women, 1944; Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
    Author: Roy Hudson
  - Item 2: Communists and the trade unions, 1943; Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Trends in the labor movement, 1941; Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: The growth of the trade unions, 1941; Publication (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Box: 24, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Towards a classless society, 1947; Publication (Box 24, Folder 8)
    Author: H. D. Hughes
- Box: 24, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The crisis; the unions and the courts, the tyranny of injunctions, the power of unity, 1909; Publication (Box 24, Folder 9)
    Author: Robert Hunter
- Box: 24, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Industrial mobility, a peaceful and powerful weapon to settle our economic problems and promote friendly relations among men, 1912; Publication (Box 24, Folder 10)
    Author: Judson B. Hurd
- Box: 24, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: 3 A.M., Publication (Box 24, Folder 11)
    Author: Fannie Hurst
- Box: 24, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Eugene V. Debs: an introduction, 1900; Publication (Box 24, Folder 12)
    Author: Walter Hurt
- Box: 24, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: What every working woman wants, 1935; Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
    Author: Grace Hutchins
  - Item 2: Youth in industry, 1932; Publication (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Box: 24, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: What are you going to do about it?: The case for constructive peace, 1936; Publication (Box 24, Folder 14)
    Author: Aldous Huxley
- Box: 24, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Communism at work, 1953; Publication (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Author: Douglas Arnold Hyde
- Box: 24, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Keep America out of War: Unite for Peace, Freedom and Socialism, 1939; Publication (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Author: Independent Labor League of America
- Box: 24, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The changing structure of trade unions: an inquiry, 1953; Publication (Box 24, Folder 17)
    Author: Independent Labour Party (Great Britain)
- Box: 24, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The independent trade unions, 1970; Publication (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Box: 24, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The grave-diggers of Russia: shall we recognize the promoters of world revolution?, Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Author: Industrial Defense Association
  - Item 2: Does the CIO seek to promote red revolution?, Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: The Jewish refugee problem, and The egregious Gentile called to account, 1939; Publication (Box 24, Folder 19)
    Author: Grover Cleveland Hall; Bruce Bliven
- Box: 24, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Industrial efficiency: a consideration of factors necessary in winning the war and in taking our place in world trade after the war., Publication (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Box: 24, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Industrial socialism: its message to the workers, origin, aims, and tactics, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 21)
    Author: Industrial Socialist Propaganda League of New York
- Box: 24, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: 50 million captive women, 1956; Publication (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Author: Institute of International Labor Research
- Box: 24, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Arbeiter-Fursorge auf den fustensteiner, Publication (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Box: 24, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Bulletin of the Industrial Commission of Ohio, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: Industrial Commission of Ohio
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.13
  - Item 2: A resume of the arguments against state insurance, 1914; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: Workmen's Compensation Publicity Bureau
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.14
  - Item 3: Comments on the Workmen's compensation bill recommended in the Majority report of the Iowa employers liability and workmens compensation commission, 1912; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: P. Tecumseh Sherman
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.15. letter to Welker Given, esq., secretary Iowa employers' liability and workmen's compensation commission
  - Item 4: A criticism of the Ohio law of workmen's, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.16. Address before the Business men's club, of Cincinnati, January 18th, 1913
  - Item 5: Invasion of the insurance field by the state, 1914; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.17
  - Item 6: The progressive cost of workmen's compensation, 1914; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.18
  - Item 7: Administration of workmen's compensation benefits under the Michigan law: methods of procedure: labors view point, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: Claude O. Talyoer
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.19
  - Item 8: Workmen's accident compensation and insurance in Belgium, Norway, Sweden, Denmark and Italy, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: Harold G. Villard
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.20. A series of letters by Harold G. Villard
  - Item 9: Workmen's accident insurance in Germany, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.21
  - Item 10: Casualty insurance under the negligence laws, 1914; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.1
  - Item 11: Workmen's compensation and employer's liability insurance in Ohio, 1914; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: Edwin Wilmore Davis
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.2. Address before the Insurance Federation of Ohio, Cleveland, May 6th, 1914 / by E.W. Davis.
  - Item 12: The economic and essential functions of the insurance company in the administration of a compensation law, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: Richard L. Drake
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.3. An address delivered at the third annual convention of the International Association of Casualty and Surety Underwriters, Quebec, Canada, July 9, 1913.
  - Item 13: Extracts from letters showing the attitude of organized labor and workmens compensations laws., 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: William Temple Emmet
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.4
  - Item 14: The workmen's compensation situation in New York state, 1914; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: Frank Hasbrouck
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.5. Paper read by Frank Hasbrouck, superintendent of insurance of the state of New York, at the National convention of insurance commissioners, Asheville, North Carolina, September 17, 1914.
  - Item 15: The case against state insurance, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: William H. Hotchkiss
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.6. Together with an editorial on workmen's compensation.
  - Item 16: Bulletin. Workmen's compensation act, 1912; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.7
  - Item 17: Workmen's compensation law of the State of Iowa, 1914; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.8
  - Item 18: Rules and regulations and rules of procedure of the industrial commission of Ohio, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.9. Under the provisions of section 22 of the workmen's compensation act
  - Item 19: Employers' liability and workmen's compensation laws, 1912; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Author: J. Walter Lord
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.10
  - Item 20: The Workmen's compensation law of New York state, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.11. Printed in advance from the thirteenth annual report of the commissioner of labor. James M. Lynch, comissioner.
  - Item 21: Amended Senate bill no 48, 1913; Publication (Box 24, Folder 24)
    Notes: Insurance pamphlets 7:no.12. n act to futher define the powers, duties and jurisdiction of the state liability board of awards with reference to the collection, mainenance and disbursement of the state insurance fund for the benefit of injured, and the de
- Box: 25, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Integrity, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    Notes: May, 1950, Vol.4, No.7
- Box: 25, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Draft proposal: manifesto of the International Black Workers Congress., 1971; Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    Author: International Black Workers Congress
- Box: 25, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The International Labour Organisation memebership of the United States and its possibilities, 1935; Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Author: E.J. Phelan; Manley O. Hudson; James T. Shotwell.
- Box: 25, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A report of proceedings and decisions of the first International Conference of Negro Workers, 1930; Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Author: International Conference of Negro Workers
    Notes: July 1930.
- Box: 25, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: International runaway shop, 1972; Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Author: Mitch Zimmerman
- Box: 25, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Amendments to the Wagner Act, 1939; Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Box: 25, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: International Trade Union unity, 1925; Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Box: 25, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The concentration of wealth: its cause and cure: plea for the labor exchange, 1896; Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
    Author: Edward Irving
- Box: 25, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Sherman Act: anti-trust or anti-labor?, 1940; Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
    Author: A. J. Isserman
- Box: 25, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The truth about Communism in Hawaii, 1947; Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Author: Ichiro Izuka
- Box: 25, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: ERA: ratifying equality, 1975; Publication (Box 25, Folder 11)
    Author: Carolyn J. Jacobson
- Box: 25, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Westbrook Pegler unmasked, 1947; Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)
    Author: Henry Jager
- Box: 25, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Anarchism and Malthus, 1910; Publication (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Author: C. L. James
- Box: 25, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Soviet China, 1932; Publication (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Author: Maurice James; Richard Doonping
- Box: 25, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Social-democracy and the war, 1940; Publication (Box 25, Folder 15)
    Author: V. J. Jerome
- Box: 25, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Jewish Labor Bund, 1897-1957, 1958; Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Author: International Jewish Labor Bund
  - Item 2: A tribute to William Green, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Author: Jewish Labor Committee
  - Item 3: Fear, frustration, backlash: the new crisis in civil rights, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Author: Bayard Rustin
  - Item 4: Labor looks at the crisis in civil rights, 1959; Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Author: Harry Golden
  - Item 5: Pioneers of labor, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Statements and resolutions adopted by the Third World Conference of the Bund, 1955; Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Notes: April 8 - 15, 1955, Montreal, Canada.
  - Item 7: The Jewish Labor Movement in America: two views., 1957; Publication (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Box: 25, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Robert Owen, idealist, 1917; Publication (Box 25, Folder 17)
    Author: C. E. M. Joad
- Box: 25, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The job Australia is doing, 1942; Publication (Box 25, Folder 18)
    Author: Australian News and Information Bureau
- Box: 25, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Jobs, security, democracy and peace, 1938; Publication (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Author: Communist Party of the United States of America (Mass.)
- Box: 25, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Marxism and the intellectuals: the working class and socialism, 1962; Publication (Box 25, Folder 20)
    Author: C. L. R. James; J. R. Johnson; Raymond Williams
    Notes: Review of two books by British socialist Raymond Williams plus documentary material on the destruction of a workers paper in the U. S. / by J. R. Johnson [i. e. C. L. R. James].
- Box: 25, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Speeches and editorials, Publication (Box 25, Folder 21)
    Author: Daniel De Leon; Olive M. Johnson
- Box: 25, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: America faces Japan, 1941; Publication (Box 25, Folder 22)
    Author: William Crane Johnstone
- Box: 25, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Seamen and longshoremen under the Red flag, 1935; Publication (Box 25, Folder 23)
    Author: Hays Jones
- Box: 25, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Trade unionism in Malaya, 1954; Publication (Box 25, Folder 24)
    Author: Alex Josey
- Box: 25, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: India in revolt, 1942; Publication (Box 25, Folder 25)
    Author: Henry Judd; Max Shachtman
- Box: 25, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Behind the Bertrand Russell case, 1940; Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
    Author: Horace Meyer Kallen
- Box: 25, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Meet the man who plans to rule America, 1958; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
    Author: Joseph P. Kamp
  - Item 2: We do not believe in God, said Walter Reuther: a concise critical commentary, 1958; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: The bigots behind the swastika spree, 1960; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 4: Election guide for voters who don't like Ike or Adlai, 1956; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: The greater danger, 1960; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
    Notes: An election guide for Democrats, Republicans, Catholics and anti-Catholics, conservatives, constitutionalists, states righters, third partyites, anti-Communists, union members and particularly for voters who don't like Nixon or Kennedy
  - Item 6: The lowdown on Little Rock and the plot to sovietize the South, 1957; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 7: Behind the plot to sovietize the South, 1956; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 8: Trickery, treachery, tyranny and treason in Washington, 1957; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 9: About the man who will win the 1956 election!, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 10: Strikes and the communists behind them, 1947; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 11: WHO tells your Congressman how to vote? Who makes him violate his oath?, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 12: Vote CIO and get a soviet America, 1944; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 13: The fifth column stops defense, 1941; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 14: Join the C.I.O. and help build a soviet America., 1937; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Box: 25, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Socialist Party at the cross roads, 1934; Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
    Author: Hayim Kantorovits
- Box: 25, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Karen Silkwood: union sister, 1946-1974, 1978; Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
    Author: Richard L. Rashke; Alison Freedman
- Box: 26, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Stop union raiding, 1962; Publication (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Author: William Kashtan
- Box: 26, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Unemployment in the USSR and the struggle against it, 1927; Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Author: A. Katz
  - Item 2: Protection of labour in the U.S.S.R., 1927; Publication (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Box: 26, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Who fights for a free Cuba?, 1933; Publication (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Author: Martin Kaye; Louise Perry
- Box: 26, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Unemployment in an administration of prosperity, 1928; Publication (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Author: Edward Keating
- Box: 26, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Keir Hardie Calendar, Publication (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Author: James Keir Hardie
- Box: 26, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Beyond New Leftism, 1969; Publication (Box 26, Folder 6)
    Author: Steven Kelman
- Box: 26, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Build for socialism!: a manual on organization, 1920; Publication (Box 26, Folder 7)
    Author: Harold Kelso
- Box: 26, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Unemployment and its problems, 1935; Publication (Box 26, Folder 8)
    Author: John C. Kennedy
- Box: 26, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Wages and the working day, 1946; Publication (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Author: John Keracher
- Box: 26, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Unions and union leaders of their own choosing, 1957; Publication (Box 26, Folder 10)
    Author: Clark Kerr
- Box: 26, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Revolt among the sharecroppers, 1936; Publication (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Author: Howard Kester
- Box: 26, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: What is democratic Socalism?, 1943; Publication (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Author: Carlyle King
- Box: 26, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The TVA labor relations policy at work: successful cooperation between public power and organized labor in the public interest, 1940; Publication (Box 26, Folder 13)
    Author: Judson King
- Box: 26, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Letter from Birmingham City Jail, 1963; Publication (Box 26, Folder 14)
    Author: Martin Luther King
- Box: 26, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Unemployment its causes and remedies, 1930; Publication (Box 26, Folder 15)
    Author: Willford Isbell King
- Box: 26, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Think, or surrender, 1916; Publication (Box 26, Folder 16)
    Author: George Ross Kirkpatrick
- Box: 26, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Wrecking the nation: the crime of 1907-8, true causes of the panic, stringency of money and idleness of millions of men., 1908; Publication (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Box: 26, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Justice for organized workers, Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
    Author: Louis Kirshbaum; Norman Thomas; A. J. Muste; Roger N. Baldwin; Paul H. Douglas; Paul F. Brissenden; David J. Saposs
  - Item 2: Why not labor courts?, 1939; Publication (Box 26, Folder 18)
    Author: Louis Kirshbaum
- Box: 26, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Finding a job during the depression, 1933; Publication (Box 26, Folder 19)
    Author: Harry Dexter Kitson
- Box: 26, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Tables of hourly wages: the bookkeepers assistant, 1919; Publication (Box 26, Folder 20)
    Author: Jacob Kleid
- Box: 26, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Comments on labor courts, 1939; Publication (Box 26, Folder 21)
    Author: John C. Knox
- Box: 26, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Are unions above the law?, 1955; Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
    Author: Herbert V. Kohler
    Notes: Address given before Executive's Club of Chicago, December 9, 1955.
  - Item 2: Can a free economy tolerate union violence?: the menace of UAW-CIO coercion, 1957; Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Item 3: In freedom's cause: the menace of UAW-CIO coercion, 1956; Publication (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Box: 26, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Lucile Kohn: a tribute, 1973; Publication (Box 26, Folder 23)
    Author: Lucile Kohn
    Notes: 20-Oct-73
- Box: 26, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 26, Folder 24)